techyard.net 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy & Disclaimer - TECH YARD

At **TechYard.net** we take the privacy of our visitors very seriously. Please read this Privacy Policy to learn more about how we treat personally identifiable information. We provide this Privacy Policy because you have a right to know what information we collect, how it is protected and used.

The views expressed in this blog are entirely my views and are NOT endorsed by my employer, organization, co-citizens, family, friends or co-workers.

 **Email Addresses** : When you make a comment or contact me using the contact page where your email is required. Please be assured that you email address will only be used for responding to your email or comment and will never be made publicly available. Your email address will never be sold or given away to anybody else.

 **Visitor Statistics** :This website collects visitor statistics. These statistics are collected purely to identify the number of visitors to this [web site](http://www.techyard.net/), what those visitors looked at and how long they spent browsing. The statistics gathered will only be used to judge the popularity of this web site is and to make future improvements.

 **Comments Policy** : The author does not assume responsibility over comments he did not make on this blog. While comments are welcome from anybody, we reserve the right to remove any comment that is not deemed suitable for publication. This could include but is not limited to objectional and abusive comments. Hate, racist comments, or any other form of prejudice will be removed and the poster banned! Spam in any form will not be accepted.

 **Third Party Advertisers**

Advertisements appearing on **TechYard.net** may be delivered to users by one of our advertising partners. Our advertising partners may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, advertising partners (or “ad networks”) may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by **TechYard.net** and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/).

Please note that these companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/).

You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set, however, if you configure your browser to reject cookies,you may not be able to take full advantage of all offerings on the **TechYard.net** .

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a web site’s computers and stored on your computer’s hard drive.

 **Disclaimer :**

The views expressed in this site, [Techyard.net](http://www.techyard.net/) are mine and mine alone. The tips and tweaks,views mentioned are based on my experience or from another sources. I am not responsible if the tips and tweaks,ideas, or anything mentioned here did not work for you or it should cause any damage or loss under any situation. Do it under your own discretion.

If our Privacy Policies change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes .

 **NOTE:** ** ** This Policy is subject to change anytime at my sole discretion and any changes made will be effective immediately.

[Last Update] – April 2nd, 2009.
